(Penny:)I don't know, Sheldon.
(Penny:)Are you Star Wars?
(Sheldon:)How can one person be a whole movie?
(Penny:)Okay, I give up.
Can we just do something else?
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)I was Spock.
(Sheldon:)Are you and Leonard
friends with benefits?
(Raj:)What?
(Sheldon:)Are you and Leonard
friends with benefits?
Where did that even come from?
(Penny:)- Did he say we were?
- No, Leonard said nothing.
(Sheldon:)But who knows what goes on over here when
he pretends your mail was misdelivered?
(Penny:)Just mail, no benefits.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Penny:)Why are you asking?
(Sheldon:)I'm curious about
the whole social construct.
(Sheldon:)On its face, the idea of satisfying
one's sexual appetite...
(Sheldon:)Assuming one is afflicted with such.
(Sheldon:)...without emotional entanglement,
that seems imminently practical.
(Sheldon:)What I've observed, however,
is Howard Wolowitz crying like a little girl.